webmasterslibrary.com 2008-12-17

# Privacy Statement - Webmasters' Library

### Privacy Statement

This page discloses the processing and use of data collected while visiting WebmastersLibrary.com. Your privacy as a visitor of WebmastersLibrary.com and an Internet user is important to us. We will do everything possible to ensure your privacy is respected in all dealings with Webmasters' Library.

#### Location of Service:

  * The creator of Webmasters' Library, Brad Culbert, is based in Queensland, Australia
  * Webmasters' Library is hosted by Webstrike Solutions in Colorado, USA

#### Collection of Data:

You can access our website without disclosing personally identifiable information. We do not automatically log personal data, nor do we link information automatically logged by other means with personal data about specific individuals.

Users have the option of subscribing to the Webmasters' Library email newsletter. Email addresses collected from subscriptions to the Webmasters' Library newsletter are not sold, or disclosed to any third parties. These addresses will only be used to send communications related to Webmasters' Library. You will not receive any emails you did not request.

Non-identifiable web tracking data is collected to gain information about the use of our website. Information collected includes; Internet Protocol address, referring URL, browser version, page views and operating system. This information is used solely for statistical, research and development purposes and allows us to further improve the services we provide to you.

Webmasters' Library is associated with the following third party organisations. Links to respective privacy policies are provided for each:

  * Google AdSense to receive context-sensitive search results on website pages. [Google Privacy Policy](http://www.google.com/privacy.html)
  * Amazon.com for product reviews, images and purchase links. [Amazon.com Privacy Notice](http://www.amazon.com/exec/obidos/tg/browse/-/468496/102-5995969-8081749)
  * Commission Junction for webmaster-related advertising links. [Commission Junction Privacy Policy](http://www.cj.com/privacy.jsp#consumer)
  * Mailer Mailer to manage subscriptions to the Webmasters' Library Newsletter. [Mailer Mailer Privacy Policy](http://www.mailermailer.com/privacypolicy.mlm)

#### Disclosure of Personal Information:

No personal or personally identifiable information about visitors to Webmasters' Library, or subscribers to the Webmasters' Library Newsletter, is disclosed to any third parties.

#### Cookies:

Webmasters' Library itself, does not create or use any cookies in visitors browsers. However, third party content displayed on Webmasters' Library, may use anonymous cookies for traffic analysis purposes. Please see the Collection of Data section for links to these third party privacy policies.

#### External Site Links:

WWebmasters' Library contains links to external websites outside the WebmastersLibrary.com domain. We are in no way responsible for the privacy practices or content of these websites.

If you have any questions or comments regarding this privacy statement, please contact us.
